<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Venture Adventure</string>
    <string name="welcomeMessage">A Choose-Your-Own Adventure Story of a Young Entrepreneur</string>
    <string name="startAdventure">Start the adventure \=\></string>
    <string name="chapter1">Chapter 1</string>
    <string name="chapter2">Chapter 2</string>
    <string name="chapter3">Chapter 3</string>
    <string name="chapter4">Chapter 4</string>
    <string name="chapter5">Chapter 5</string>
    <string name="chapter6">Chapter 6</string>
    <string name="chapter7">Chapter 7</string>
    <string name="chapter8">Chapter 8</string>
    <string name="chapter9">Chapter 9</string>
    <string name="continueText">Continue</string>
    <string name="optionsText">You choose what happens next: </string>
    <string name="endText">End the story.</string>
    <string name="part_1">
        The city center was swirling with activity. There must have been a thousand different things to look at,
        but Buzz was admiring one thing. Not too far off was a group of people holding some sort of meeting.
        It was a fairly diverse group- some old some young, some tall some short, some men some women- but they
        all had one thing in common: wealth.
        \n\nBuzz had never known wealth. He came from a modest home where his mother and brother had enough but not
        usually much more than that. He wondered what it be like to be wealthy.
        \n\nBuzz walked past this spot frequently to see the Professor. The Professor was not actually a professor
        anymore. He gave up teaching at the college to teach at the local high school “where the real lessons
        need to be taught,” he would often say. Buzz had the Professor as a teacher a couple years ago, but he
        continued to talk with him often. In Buzz’s opinion, the Professor was the wisest person he had ever met.
        And Buzz was probably right.
        \n\n“What is on your mind?” the Professor asked.
        \n\n“Oh, nothing. I was just looking at those nicely dressed people over there,” Buzz replied.
        \n\n“Ah yes. Those are a group of investors, if I am not mistaken. It looks like they are discussing a large
        business proposition,” the Professor explained.
        \n\n“They are all wealthy, huh?” Buzz guessed.
        \n\n“Most of them are, but they were not always wealthy. Many of them have started businesses of their own to
        get to where they are,” reported the professor.
        \n\nBuzz stuck around a few more minutes while the professor explained how a lot of the wealthy people in the
        community had started successful businesses, and how businesses can help people to become wealthy.
        \n\n“Starting a business involves taking risks, but, to gain wealth, you have to take risks.” The professor added,
        “the key is to take risks wisely.”
        \n\nThose words stuck in Buzz’s head as he traveled home for dinner. He wondered if he could start a business
        himself one day. Maybe he would become wealthy, he thought. As he went to bed that night, he could not stop
        thinking about what the professor said.
    </string>
    <string name="part_1_boxed_section">In many areas of the world, the best way to earn a living or to become wealthy is
        to start a business. Like the Professor explained, it is important to take those risks wisely
    </string>
    <string name="part_2">The next morning, Buzz woke up after having a very vivid dream. In his dream, he had started a
        successful business and he was wealthy.
        \n\n“What a crazy dream…” Buzz though. “I wonder if that would ever come true one day.” Buzz though he really didn’t
        know much about starting or owning a business. “Oh well,” he said dismissively.
        \n\n“Morning, Buzz!” his little brother greeted him.
        \n\n“Morning, Leo.” His little brother was such a happy kid. Buzz was lucky to have him as a brother. Buzz considered
        his little brother to be his best friend. Buzz turned to his mom. “Good morning, Mom.”
        \n\n“Good morning, Buzz,” his mom smiled back.
        \n\n“Hey Mom, do we have any bread?” Buzz asked his mom as they sat at breakfast. “Don’t you think eggs go well with
        bread?”
        \n\nHis mom agreed. “I do think eggs go well with bread, but we do not have any bread today. The bakery is a good half
        hour walk one way.” She looked at Buzz and Leo and smiled. They smiled back. “I’ll get some more bread sometime
        next week.”
        \n\nAfter breakfast, Buzz walked his brother to his brother’s school and continued on the path towards his own school.
        The path led next to a large fish store.  Buzz paused. “Frankie’s Fish”, Buzz read the sign aloud.
        \n\n“How can I help you?” a voice came from inside the store’s porch. Buzz hadn’t even noticed the man. The fish salesman
        exited the shade of the porch and offered Buzz a smile. “Are you looking for fish?”
        \n\n“Oh, no. Thank you, though.” Buzz blushed a bit. He was just reading the sign. He had not noticed the sign before.
        “Hey,” Buzz continued, “who is Frankie?”
        \n\nThe man gave another smile and said “well, Frankie is the owner.” He searched Buzz’s eyes to see if that answered
        his question. “Frankie owns ‘Frankie’s Fish’. He started this shop over ten years ago. He is usually not here since
        he has people run the store for him, but he is actually here today.” The man thought for a second the continued
        “would you like to meet him?”
        \n\nBuzz accepted the invitation. Frankie had started a business. Maybe he could tell Buzz how to start a business.
        Frankie came out of the store, full of smiles. His hands were rough from years of hard work, but a little softer
        than they used to be as Frankie now had more time to spend doing things other than work over these past few years.
        Frankie greeted Buzz and the two started a discussion about how Frankie started ‘Frankie’s Fish’. Buzz learned all
        sorts of good things, and he felt really encouraged about one day starting his own business.
        \n\n“But how did you know it was going to work?” Buzz asked near the end of the conversation. It was getting close to
        when school would start.
        \n\n“Well,” Frankie replied, “I did not know for sure that I would be successful, but you know what made me believe I
        would be successful?” Frankie paused for dramatic effect. He knew this was a nugget of wisdom that a young man like
        Buzz could profit from if he understood it. “I believed I would be successful because I saw a need. I saw that there
        was a need in this town for a fish store, and I could help meet that need. That is why I thought I would be successful.”
        That nugget of wisdom would not be lost on Buzz. Buzz thought about it for a moment before realizing he really did
        need to leave for school now.
        \n\n“Thank you for your time mister Frank!” Buzz concluded. “I have to go to school.”
        \n\n“No worries, Buzz. And please, call me Frankie.” Frankie watched as Buzz galloped off towards school.
    </string>
    <string name="part_2_boxed_section">Part of what made Frankie successful in his fish business was that he saw a need for
        selling fish in the town. To be successful as an entrepreneur, it is important to find a need or to find something
        that people would be willing to pay money for.
    </string>
    <string name="part_3">
        Later that night he sat with his mom and little brother for dinner. His mom had made fish. After they had all chatted
        about their day a little bit, Buzz asked “Mom, did you buy this fish from ‘Frankie’s Fish’?”
        \n\n“I did,” she replied. “I always buy our fish from there. They have quality fish for a very good price, and they are
        nice to their customers. Why do you ask?”
        \n\nBuzz explained. “I met Frankie today. We talked a little bit about how he started his business. He is a really nice guy.
        He told me all about how to start a fishing business.”
        \n\nHis mom was proud of Buzz for talking to Frankie and learning about his business. “That is fantastic that you talked
        with him,” she said warmly. She continued, “I have never met Frankie myself, but I have met Maria.”
        \n\n“Who is Maria?” inquired Buzz.
        \n\n“You know how we have eggs for breakfast?” His mom began. “Maria owns the egg store where we get our eggs. We always
        get our eggs from Maria.” She went on to explain that Maria started her eggs business five years ago. Maria started
        small and has grown to provide eggs for most of the people in the town. Buzz could see that his mom was very proud of
        Maria. “She was a normal person who had a great idea and took a chance on starting a business. She did a good thing for
        herself, and for others since everyone on this side of town can get fresh eggs easily.”
        \n\nBuzz enjoyed the story. He had no idea where the eggs came from before then. And Maria was a normal person with a good
        idea, his mom had said. A normal person can start a business, he thought. As he got ready to sleep, he asked himself
        “should I try to start a business?”
    </string>
    <string name="part_3_option_1_good">
        Buzz decides to start a business.
    </string>
    <string name="part_3_option_2_bad">
        Buzz decides not to start a business.
    </string>
    <string name="part_3_result_option_2_bad">
        Buzz had been really excited to start a business, but that excitement faded over time. “I should be realistic,” he
        told himself. Starting a business did not sound very realistic. Also, it would be easier not to try to start a
        business. If he tried to start a business, he might fail.
        \n\nOver the next few weeks, Buzz instead tried to find a part time job. He was close to being done with school, and he
        needed to help support his family. It took some time, but eventually Buzz found a part time job at a local store. He
        stocked the shelves and kept the place clean. It was a terribly boring job, but he made some money doing it.
        \n\nAfter a month or two of working there he received some unfortunate news. The store owner, who had hired him just months
        before, told Buzz that he would have to let Buzz go. The owner had sold his business to another company who planned to
        change up the store. Unfortunately, the company already had enough employees, and his job was going to be eliminated.
        \n\nBuzz felt really blue about the news, so he went for a really long walk to try to think through what he should
        do. Either he would now try to start a business, or he could look for another job.
    </string>
    <string name="part_3B_option_1_good">
        Buzz decides to start a business.
    </string>
    <string name="part_3B_option_2_bad">
        Buzz decides to look for another job.
    </string>
    <string name="part_3B_result_option_2_bad">
        Buzz spent the next month searching for work. Eventually he settled for a job that he did not want. It did not pay
        much, and he was not likely to learn much doing the work. However, he stuck with it. He stayed in his job for years,
        actually. He felt that the job was sucking the life out of him, but he appreciated that is was stable.
        \n\nHe sometimes had the urge to try to start a business, but he suppressed the urge. Eventually instead of having
        the desire to start a business, he just thought wishfully about it. He wondered what would have become of his life
        if he had tried to start a business. He saw new businesses start up in his town and thought how that might have been
        exciting to be the one to start that up.
        \n\n“Oh, well”, Buzz thought. “Some people are just not meant to have success,” he said with a sigh.
        \n\nThis is the end of the story, but would you like to know what would have happened to Buzz if he tried to start
        a business?
    </string>
    <string name="part_4">
        This morning Buzz woke up feeling good about starting a business. As he came to the table for breakfast, he looked at the
        eggs his mom had made. “Maria’s eggs,” he said.
        \n\n“That is right,” his mom replied.
        \n\n“I am going to start a business like Maria did,” Buzz announced.
        \n\n“That is wonderful, Buzz,” his mom encouraged. She then added “it will not be easy, you know.”
        \n\n“I know, but I am going to do it,” Buzz replied.
        \n\nLeo joined in on the encouragement. “I am sure you can do, it Buzz. You are smart.” That made Buzz smile. “Hey Mom,” Leo
        said moving on, “do we have any bread today?”
        \n\nHis mom answered, “sorry, Leo. We do not have bread today.”
        \n\nBuzz only partially heard the rest of the conversation. His mind was wandering through the possibilities of starting a
        business. He definitely wanted to do it. He just needed to figure out what type of business to start.
        \n\nBuzz thought about it most of the day. Sometime around lunch he decided, he could not wait to tell his family that
        evening.
        \n\n“I am going to start a fishing business like Frankie” Buzz told his family during dinner.
        \n\n“Fishing, huh?” his mother replied.
        \n\n“Yeah, Frankie already told me a bunch about it, he was already successful at it, so I could be too,” Buzz said
        confidently.
        \n\nHis mom looked a bit worried. “Frankie’s Fish already has low prices, lots of variety, and everyone trusts them…” she
        pointed out.
        \n\n“I think I will start fishing tomorrow, and then try to sell it. Frankie said he started small like that,” Buzz reported.
        \n\nHis mom’s comment hadn’t registered yet.
        \n\nHis mom replied, “that may be how the business started, but now it is quite the fish store to compete with. You could
        also consider trying to start a different sort of business.”
        \n\nBuzz had liked the idea of a fish story because he already knew how to fish, but he could consider starting a different
        kind of business. “Like what?” said Buzz.
        \n\n“Well,” his mom was searching her brain for an idea, “I am sure there are lots of good options.”
        \n\nThe room was silent for a moment.
        \n\nThen Leo piped up. “How about a bakery?”
        \n\n“Oh, that is a good idea!” His mom said with relief.
        \n\n“But I don’t know how to make bread,” Buzz said with mild objection.
        \n\nHis mom was quick to encourage “I am sure you could learn. I have made bread before, and it is not too hard to do.”
        \n\nBuzz did like the idea. He liked bread.
        \n\n“And,” his mom added with a smile “I sure would appreciate the two of you not asking me for bread all the time.”
        \n\nThat was a lot to think about. Buzz was serious about starting a business, and this was a really big decision. He didn’t
        know how to make bread, but maybe there really was a need for it.
    </string>
    <string name="part_4_option_1_bad">
        Buzz tries to start a fishing business.
    </string>
    <string name="part_4_option_2_good">
        Buzz tries to start a bakery.
    </string>
    <string name="part_4_result_option_1_bad">
        Buzz decided to go ahead and start a fishing business. The next day, Buzz spent half of the day fishing and half of
        the day trying to sell his fish. He had woken up really early to try to get a good catch before the day was too hot. By
        mid- morning he had a group of fish that he could sell, so he hurried to the city center where vendors often sold things.
        \n\nHe found a spot where people would see him and his fish. He even made a sign, so he might attract people. “Fresh
        fish!” He yelled. No one seemed interested.
        \n\nAfter an hour or two, he was feeling pretty discouraged. He asked himself why no one was buying the fish. Then he
        asked people who were passing by. “Excuse me, do you know why no one around here is buying my fish?” He asked a few
        different people before someone gave him an answer.
        \n\nThey told him that they already buy their fish from Frankie’s Fish. It is quality and well-priced, and they always
        have a good variety. It sounded like what his mom had said. He did not stop at one answer, but as fate would have it,
        the next three people he asked told him almost the same exact thing. Eventually Buzz did sell some of his fish that day,
        but he had already caught on to how hard it would be to sell fish while people could get fish from Frankie’s Fish. Buzz
        headed home with his remaining unsold fish.
        \n\n“I think I might start a bakery,” he reported to his family that night at dinner.
        \n\n“Well, we loved the fish you brought back,” his mom said. She knew failing was never easy.
        \n\nBuzz chuckled. “I am glad we could use the fish, at least. But it was just like you said. Everyone already goes to Frankie’s Fish. I think I could still sell some fish, but it would be really hard to start a fish business in the same town as Frankie’s Fish.”
        \n\nBuzz was deep in thought as he drifted off to sleep that night. “I can do this,” he said to himself. “I just need to figure out how.”
    </string>
    <string name="part_4_result_option_1_bad_boxed_section">
        Part of being successful in starting a business is finding a need that is not yet being filled or that you could fill
        better. To be successful at his fishing business, Buzz would have needed to find a way to compete with Frankie’s Fish.
    </string>
    <string name="part_5">
        Buzz woke up the next morning, excited about the prospect of starting a bakery. Where to start? “The Professor!” he
        thought. “He would know what to start with.” Buzz went to school early that day and found the Professor so he could ask
        how to start a bakery.
        \n\nBuzz told the Professor about his bakery idea. The Professor was proud of Buzz. “I like it! How do you plan to start?”
        \n\n“That is what I wanted to ask you,” Buzz admitted. “Where should I start?”
        \n\n“Okay,” responded the Professor. “Tell me what you have thought of so far.”
        \n\nBuzz thought for a second. He had thought about it but had not written anything down. “Well, I know I need to learn to
        make bread…” Buzz began. “…and then I need to sell it. I was just going to use my Mom’s kitchen. Maybe I could sell it
        at school or maybe from our house.”
        \n\n“Those are all great thoughts,” the Professor reassured him. “There is nothing wrong with starting in your mother’s
        kitchen. It is usually a good idea to start small and with low costs, if possible. Selling at school could be good. You
        could take orders from there and then the next day bring the bread that people ordered. You could even deliver the bread,
        if you wanted.”
        \n\nBuzz nodded. Start in his mother’s kitchen. Sell at school. Take orders there. Deliver maybe.
        \n\nThe Professor continued. “Sorry. I am getting ahead of myself. I am just excited for you. I think the first place to
        start, actually, is pressure testing your value proposition.”
        \n\n“What is a pressure test?” Buzz said with a worried face.
        \n\n“Oh, just a term of speech. I mean to say that you should see if your idea is a good one. You could write out what you
        are going to do and why people would want to buy your product. Next you can find out if people will be willing to buy
        that product.”
        \n\n“Okay.” Said Buzz. “How would I do that?”
        \n\n“Sometimes just trying to sell the product is a good way to see if people will buy it. However, that can be risky if you
        put a lot of time and effort in to making something only to find out that people do not even want what you made. So, one
        way to make it less risky would be to try to find out if people will buy what you are going to make even before you make
        it. You could ask people if they would be interested in buying bread from you. If you get a good response from that then
        you could bring some bread and see if people would be willing to buy it.”
        \n\nBuzz talked a bit more with the Professor and left feeling very encouraged. He liked the Professor’s idea of trying to
        find out if it is a good idea before spending the time making it. It was going to take him some time to learn to make the
        bread, anyway.
        \n\nBuzz asked friends at school, and he asked his friends to ask their parents and see if they would be interested in
        buying bread. Buzz got nothing but positive feedback. Buzz had found a good idea because it really filled a need.
    </string>
    <string name="part_5_boxed_section">
        The first step in creating a business is often to create the “value proposition” or what value the business brings. It is
        also a good idea whenever possible to do some research to find if people would be willing to pay for your product
    </string>
    <string name="part_6">
        Learning to bake was not as hard as he thought. His mom and brother enjoyed tasting the practice loaves (when they tasted
        good). He soon was confident at making bread.
        \n\nHe brought some sample bread to school to give to those who said they would be willing to buy the bread. They enjoyed
        the bread! They began to be excited about having fresh bread more often. Buzz could not be happier.
        \n\n“So how much does a loaf cost?” A friend asked.
        \n\nBuzz was caught off guard. He had not even thought about how much to charge for his bread. “Well,” he began, “it won’t
        be free… and it won’t be too expensive… Let me get back to you on that.” The friend seemed satisfied with the answer for
        now.
        \n\nBuzz went straight to the Professor. “I have a problem.”
        \n\n“What is it?” the Professor said with concern.
        \n\n“My friends are asking me how much to charge for my bread and I don’t know what to say,” Buzz explained.
        \n\n“That sounds like a good problem to have,” the Professor said with a smile. “So, you brought your bread to school,
        and they
        liked the bread?”
        \n\n“Yes,” Buzz said as a smile came across his face.
        \n\n“Congratulations. You have a solid value proposition. So, yes, next would be pricing, I suppose. This is a very
        important
        aspect about selling a product.” The Professor glanced at Buzz before beginning an impromptu lesson. “Let us start with
        what profit means. Profits is how much money a company makes after it has paid for everything. It is equal to all of the
        revenue (which is money that the business brings in) minus all of the costs. In order for your business to be successful,
        your business will need to make more revenue than cost.”
        \n\n“Got it, I think. I need to make more money by selling the bread than it cost for me to make the bread.” Buzz said,
        trying to internalize what the Professor was saying.
        \n\n“Exactly. So, for pricing, you can consider two things. One, what is your minimum price? Two, what are people willing
        to
        pay?” The Professor paused. “Let us start with the first one. What does it cost you to make a loaf of bread?”
        \n\n“Well, I spend five dollars on the ingredients, and I was able to make ten loaves of bread,” Buzz said. He thought
        for a
        second and then continued, “so it cost me a half of dollar per loaf of bread. That would be my minimum, then. I cannot
        charge less than half a dollar.”
        \n\n“Correct,” the Professor said proudly. “The next thing to consider is how much people are willing to pay. For that, it
        would be good to look at what people do now. Do you know how much people pay to buy bread now?”
        \n\nBuzz had gone with his mother to buy bread before. It was in a neighboring town, so they did not go frequently. “I
        think
        a loaf of bread cost two dollars where my mom gets it, and she is usually pretty good about finding good prices.”
        \n\n“That gives us some margin to work with. You could consider pricing above that. Since it will be more convenient for
        people to buy from you, they may be willing to pay two and a half dollars, for example. And you could consider pricing
        below that which may encourage people to start buying your bread instead of the other bread even for people in the
        neighboring town. However, you need to remember that you want your business to make a profit, and you have limited time.”
        \n\n“This makes sense.” Buzz paused and thought about what the Professor was teaching him.
        \n\n“One more thing. You do not need to worry too much about this right now while you are starting out, but this will
        become
        more important later. You should keep the business’s money separate from your own money. You ideally would have the
        business pay you a salary. That way the cost of your time is taken into consideration. Also, that way you also have a
        more clear idea of the business’s actual profits.”
        Buzz had a confused look on his face.
        \n\n“My apologies, Buzz. One step at a time. Do not worry about that yet.” The Professor said. “If you have not already, I
        would consider writing things down about your business. You can write out your plans, then include your costs and how
        you plan to price the bread.” The Professor knew this was a lot of information to a young, budding entrepreneur, but it
        was all so important, he thought. “That can be a homework assignment of sorts.”
        \n\nBuzz smiled. That is a homework assignment that he could be excited about. All of the numbers did seem daunting
        until he
        wrote them down, but despite that, Buzz felt good about his venture.
        \n\nBuzz wrote down his expenses that night before bed. Each loaf cost half of a dollar. Bread in the neighboring town cost
        two dollars. That would be his competition. Everyone in his town had to walk a long way to get to that bread, though.
    </string>
    <string name="part_6_option_1_bad1">
        Buzz chooses to price the bread at half a dollar per loaf.
    </string>
    <string name="part_6_option_2_good">
        Buzz chooses to price the bread at 2 dollars per loaf.
    </string>
    <string name="part_6_option_3_bad2">
        Buzz chooses to price the bread at 5 dollars per loaf.
    </string>
    <string name="part_6_result_option_1_bad1">
        Buzz wanted to sell as many loaves possible, so he decided to price as low as possible. A half a dollar was the
        minimum price, right? I will price at a half a dollar and I will get tons of business.
        \n\nEveryone was very surprised that the Buzz’s bread was so cheap. His friends ordered so much bread he did not know
        if he could keep up with the demand. What a success this would be!
        \n\nThat night Buzz spent the entire night baking bread. He could barely keep his eyes open during school, but he was
        very happy that he had fulfilled all the orders. More orders came in the next day. There is no way he could keep this up.
        \n\nHe counted out how much money he had made, and he barely had enough to buy ingredients for the next day. Why did
        he think pricing as low as possible was a good idea? He did the math again that night and found that he really was not
        making any money despite his hard work. He determined to raise the price.
    </string>
    <string name="part_6_result_option_3_bad2">
        Buzz wanted to maximize his profit so why not price really high? He chose to set his price at five dollars per
        loaf. He would make four and half dollars of profit per loaf!
        \n\nWhen he told his friends at school, most of those who said they were interested told him they were no longer
        interested. He did have a few orders, which he was happy to fulfill. When he brought the bread the next day, his
        customers were happy to take the bread, but at the same time they seemed to be unhappy with the exchange. The
        following week he tried to talk to them again about buying bread, but they said they were no longer interested.
        \n\nFive dollars gave him a lot of profit per loaf, but he was not doing good for his customers. That was too much
        money for a single loaf. The next day he decided to lower his price.
    </string>
    <string name="part_6_result_option_2_good">
        Buzz decided to price his bread at two dollars per loaf. He figured he would still get plenty of business because
        his bread would be more convenient for people who lived in his side of town. Also, he thought his bread tasted better,
        anyway.
        \n\nIt turned out that Buzz was right, at least about getting plenty of business. He got enough orders to keep him
        very busy. He soon had orders regular enough to have ten loaves ordered five days each week. His business was becoming
        successful!
        \n\nHe told the Professor about his success. The Professor was beaming with pride. He asked how much profit his business
        had made. That stumped Buzz for a minute. The Professor offered some help. “You can find your business’s profit by
        adding up all of the revenue (so price per loaf times how many loaves) and then subtracting all of the costs from the
        revenue. If you have already priced out the cost per loaf, then you could also look at how much profit per loaf and then
        multiply that by how many loaves you have sold.”
        \n\nBuzz did the math on paper. He was selling ten loaves per day for five days each week. That was fifty loaves. Each
        loaf cost him half of a dollar and sold for two dollars, so that was one and one half dollars per loaf. That multiplied
        by fifty loaves was seventy-five dollars per week. He showed the Professor his work.
        \n\n“That is fantastic, Buzz.” The Professor looked at the numbers a bit longer. “Half a dollar per loaf. How much do you
        pay per kilogram of flour?”
        \n\nBuzz and the professor talked through how Buzz could now possibly get a better deal on flour since he was buying so
        much. He could likely buy the flour in bulk and get a discount. The next day Buzz did just that. The cost per loaf was now
        only three tens of a dollar. That meant he was making 85 dollars per week in profits!
        \n\nBuzz felt that he was now really rolling in the dough.
    </string>
    <string name="part_7">
        Buzz enjoyed steady sales from his bakery business. Slowly his business started to grow as his customers told others about
        his bread. His younger brother had taken an interest in the bread making, so now they made the bread together and the work
        did not take as long. He decided to pay his brother a wage out of the profits. The wage was fair, and he still made a
        healthy profit per loaf of bread. With his brother working, Buzz realized he could actually make more loaves per week if
        people would buy them.
        \n\nThe next day as he was bringing the loaves of bread to his customers, a lady that was his mother’s age waved for him to
        come over. He came over to where the lady was.
        \n\n“Hey Buzz, I am Maria. I am a friend of your mom.” The lady said with a smile.
        \n\n“Maria! You have the egg store!” Buzz realized who the lady was.
        \n\n“That is right.” Said Maria. “And your mom told me that you have started a bakery! How is it going?”
        \n\n“It is good. Sales have been pretty steady. People say they like the bread. I hired my brother, so now I can make more
        bread. I am just trying to figure out how to get more customers more quickly, you know?” Buzz said. It occurred to him
        that Maria would be a good person to ask about business things since she started a successful business.
        \n\n“That is great, Buzz!” She could see why his mother was so proud of him. “I remember starting out. Getting customers
        can
        definitely be hard. A lot of times the business will grow just by ‘word of mouth’ as customers tell other people.”
        \n\nBuzz nodded in agreement.
        \n\nMaria continued, “you can also do some marketing. Have you tried advertisements?”
        \n\n“I do not think so. Do you mean like a commercial on the radio?” Buzz asked.
        \n\n“Well, radio is one of the ways you can advertise. I have actually tried a number of different types of advertising. I
        did a radio commercial once. It was not very targeted- it did not reach the right group of people. I now usually put an
        advertisement in the newspaper near the food section,” Maria explained.
        \n\nBuzz thanked Maria for the suggestion. They talked a little more before wishing each other a good day. Buzz left
        excited
        to put an advertisement in the newspaper.
        \n\nHe contacted the newspaper and found out what their advertisement placements cost. He could do a small add near the
        food
        section for ten dollars for the week or he could do a huge advertisement on the front of the newspaper for one hundred
        dollars for the week.
    </string>
    <string name="part_7_option_1_good">
        Buzz chooses to place a small advertisement near the food section for ten dollars for the week.
    </string>
    <string name="part_7_option_2_bad">
        Buzz chooses to place a large advertisement for one hundred dollars for the week.
    </string>
    <string name="part_7_result_option_2_bad">
        Buzz was really excited about advertising. He knew that the big advertisement was really expensive, but he thought it
        would make his business grow enough to compensate for the high cost. So, he ordered the expensive advertisement.
        \n\nLater that week he did get some extra orders, and that made him happy. He felt good about the decision until he
        started to calculate his profits for the week. The advertisement had increased the orders of bread some, so he was now
        making ninety-five dollar in profits per week. The advertisement still cost more than his whole week’s profits. The
        next week Buzz opted to reduce to the smaller advertisement for ten dollars a week.
    </string>
    <string name="part_7_result_option_1_good">
        The small advertisement seemed to be just right. He got more customers, but the advertisement was a reasonable portion
        of his overall costs. He could afford to continue the small advertisement, and he did not have to worry about the large
        advertising expense.
    </string>
    <string name="part_7_result_option_1_good_boxed_section">
        Advertising is an important aspect to many businesses. The small advertisement was just right for Buzz’s business.
    </string>
    <string name="part_7_conclusion">
        Buzz told the Professor about what he learned from Maria.
        \n\n“That is great. Networking can really help your business now and in the future.” The Professor said.
        \n\n“What is networking?” Buzz asked the Professor.
        \n\nThe Professor thought for a second of how to define networking. “Networking is simply interacting with others and
        exchanging ideas. You talking with Maria is an example of networking. As you meet other business owners, you can help
        each other have good ideas and can find ways that you can help each other.” The Professor looked at Buzz to see if that
        answer made sense to him before continuing. “In fact, I bet there are already ways that you and Maria could help each
        other out.”
        \n\nBuzz and the professor discussed how they could help each other. They landed on Buzz passing out business cards
        for Maria’s eggs when people buy his bread and asking that Maria pass out business cards for Buzz’s bread when customers
        buy eggs from her.
        \n\nBuzz explained the idea to Maria the next day, and Maria loved it. Soon the two businesses were helping each other
        grow, and Buzz and Maria were building a business partnership that would continue to help their businesses.
    </string>
    <string name="part_8">
        Buzz spent the next year expanding his business. He began making a variety of different types of bread, and he attracted
        a variety of types of customers- from friends to strangers to other businesses. He hired a couple of his brother’s friends
        and taught them to make the bread. Once they were confident in making the bread, the business was ready to grow to the
        next level. Buzz wanted to build a storefront where people could come to him to buy the bread. He also needed to build an
        official baking oven so he did not have to keep using his mother’s kitchen for the business.
        \n\nBuzz had stored up a respectable sum of money from the profits of the business. He had begun to pay himself a wage from
        the business’s profits, just like the Professor had mentioned at the beginning. From that point on he kept his own money
        and the money of the business separate, at the Professor’s suggestion. That way, he could see exactly how much profit the
        business was making and how much the business had to saved up to invest in something like a storefront for his bread.
        \n\nJust as Buzz was discussing with his brother what type of building the business could afford, a very professional looking
        man approached Buzz. He carried a briefcase and wore darkly-tented sunglasses.
        \n\nThe man said he had a proposition- a business loan. The man explained how much money he could get Buzz. Buzz became lost
        in
        thought for a second as he pictured a building much, much larger than the one they planned to build.
        \n\n“Plenty of businesses get a business loan like this. It can get you what you want for your business, right now. You will
        end up paying a good deal of interest, but that does not matter when you are a successful man like yourself. What
        do you say?”
        said the professional looking man.
        \n\nBuzz did not trust the man. He did, however, like the idea of having a large bakery now instead of slowly building up to
        that.
    </string>
    <string name="part_8_option_1_bad">
        Buzz chooses to take the loan.
    </string>
    <string name="part_8_option_2_good">
        Buzz chooses not to take the loan.
    </string>
    <string name="part_8_result_option_1_bad">
        Buzz could not help daydreaming of the large bakery. “That would be success,” he thought. So, Buzz took the loan.
        \n\nHe received the funds of the loans and went to work building a huge bakery. He had the money, so he hired a team of
        people to build the bakery quickly and professionally. When they finished, the bakery looked stunning.
        \n\nBuzz’s customers were very impressed at the large, beautiful bakery. His friends saw the building and told Buzz
        how amazing it was that he was already so successful. Buzz loved the building and the attention.
        \n\nThe next month the first payment of the loan came due. Wow, that was a large monthly payment. The business had
        some money saved up, so Buzz did not worry too much.
        \n\nEach month making the loan payment became more difficult. As fate would have it, Buzz’s business eventually ran
        out of money. “I am going to get out.” He said, “I cannot do this loan thing anymore.”
        \n\nBut he could not get out. He already spent the money on the large building. When he talked to the man again, he
        seemed different. He no longer pretended to be nice. He talked to the man but received no mercy. He would have to make
        the payments, or he would have to hand the business over.
        \n\nBuzz tried as hard as he could for the next three months, but he simply could not make enough money to pay off his
        debts. He sold the beautiful bakery, but it sold for much less than he paid to build it. He used that money to pay down
        the loan but there was still much more due. Buzz had never felt so terrible in his life.
        \n\nHe did not know what to do. He went to the Professor. He should have talked to the Professor before he got the loan.
        \n\n“Life is not over,” the Professor said encouragingly, “but the business venture might be over.”
        \n\nReality sunk in deep, and it hurt. That man who sold him the loan definitely did not have Buzz’s best interest at
        heart. He wished he had not taken the loan. He wished he could go back and choose to not take the loan.
        \n\nThis is the end of the story… unless you would like to go back and choose not to take the loan.
    </string>
    <string name="part_8_result_option_1_bad_go_back">
        Go back and choose not to take the loan.
    </string>
    <string name="part_8_result_option_1_bad_end_story">
        End the story.
    </string>
    <string name="part_8_result_option_2_good">
        “I am not going to take your loan,” Buzz said resolutely to the man. His brother and friends looked at him, admiring
        his resolution. They seemed to also feel that it would not be a good idea to get a business loan right now.
        \n\nWhen he told the Professor, the Professor congratulated him. “There is a time and place for loans, but there are a
        lot of times and places not for loans.”
        \n\nBuzz felt relieved. He had made the right decision about that loan.
        \n\nThe Professor added. “To make wealth you have to take risks, but you have to take them wisely.”
    </string>
    <string name="part_8_result_option_2_good_boxed_section">
        Borrowing money to start or grow a business can be a wise thing in the right circumstances. It is important to assess
        the needs and capabilities of the business. If Buzz had taken a loan that was too big for his business, it would have
        led to a painful end for his business.
    </string>
    <string name="part_9">
        Buzz and his employees finished building the bakery. It was not big, but all felt great pride in their
        accomplishment. They painted “Buzz’s Bakery” on the top of the door frame.
        \n\nAs the next few years went by, Buzz’s Bakery
        experienced great success. His partnership with Maria help both of their businesses to grow. He consulted with the
        Professor along with Maria often about how to continue to improve his business. He eventually hired more employees to
        keep up with the demand, and he also began to spend much less of his own time baking. He was still very busy leading
        the business, managing and training his team of employees, and finding ways to expand his business.
        \n\nOne day a young man
        came to the bakery asking to speak with Buzz. He was a few years younger than Buzz, and Buzz had not met him. Buzz was
        busy training a new baker when the young man came. Buzz excused himself from training the new baker, asking for an
        experienced baker to continue to help the new baker.
        \n\nAs Buzz came to the front of the bakery to talk with the young
        man, he recognized the expression on the young man’s face. The young man was trying hard to be confident, but he was
        nervous. It reminded Buzz of how he first felt when he talked to Frankie at Frankie’s Fish, so Buzz offered the young
        man a big smiled. The young man seemed relieved.
        \n\nThe young man explained that he had a business idea but that he did
        not know anything about starting a business. He had started keeping bees, and he had collected some of the honey. He
        thought that he might be able to start a business selling honey.
        \n\nThe young man paused, swallowed, and then said, “I was
        wondering if you might be willing to mentor me on how to start a business.
        \n\n”As the words hung in the air, the young
        man’s heart beat twice its usually pace. His face was held in a half squinting position as if to prepare for a blow of
        disappointment.
        \n\nBuzz had learned a lot, but there was still so much he did not know. He was not sure if he could be a
        good mentor. Also, he was very busy. He had a growing business to care for. If he did promise to mentor the young
        man, the young man would probably have a lot of questions and take away a lot of his time.
    </string>
    <string name="part_9_option_1_bad">
        Buzz wishes him good luck but tells him he is too busy.
    </string>
    <string name="part_9_option_2_good">
        Buzz promises to mentor him.
    </string>
    <string name="part_9_option_2_good_second_chance">
        Got back and Buzz promises to mentor him.
    </string>
    <string name="part_9_result_option_1_bad">
        The young man had to understand that Buzz was really busy with his own business. “Look, I hope that you are
        successful. I am just too busy to mentor you right now.” Buzz watched as the young man’s countenance fell. He felt a
        sharp pang of regret.
        \n\nThe young man looked away as he gathered himself. “I understand. You must be very busy. This is a growing
        business.” The young man had really hoped Buzz would be willing to help him out some. He would not have asked for too
        much of his time. “Thank you for your time,” he said. He resists the urge to ask again or to explain that he did not
        mean to take too much of his time. He nodded goodbye as he turned around. The young man walked away.
        \n\nBuzz regretted not having helped the young man. He tried to justify not helping. There are plenty of people that
        could mentor him. He was really busy.
        \n\nAnd he was very busy. So busy that he soon forgot all about the young man and the missed opportunity to help.
        \n\nIt was not until years later that he heard of the young man’s success. The young man had eventually found the help
        he needed to start a business. He started a large honey business. Everyone loved the honey.
        \n\nIn fact, people started traveling from other towns to buy the honey. He eventually made a partnership with a
        different bakery to recommend their bread to eat with his honey.
        \n\nWhen Buzz realized who it was that started the honey store, his mind went back to the opportunity he had to help
        him. He thought about that day and how he had justified not trying to help. He had probably had other opportunities to
        help that he did not realize, but he had been busy and had not looked around to see how he could help people.
        \n\nThe regret really hurt. He was so grateful that others had mentored him. He really should have given back. He could
        try to help others in the future, but he really did wish he could go back and try to help that young man back then.
        \n\nBuzz would continue to miss opportunities and to live with some regrets. Eventually he would learn that the real way
        to be happy is to give and to help. If only he had learned that earlier in life, he would have had a much happier life.
        \n\nThis is the end of the story, but it does not have to end this way.
    </string>
    <string name="part_9_result_option_2_good">
        Buzz thought for a moment how this young man was just like he used to be. He thought of Maria and Frankie who had taken
        the time to help him when he was just starting his business.
        \n\n“I will mentor you,” Buzz declared. “I would be happy to help you how I can.”
        \n\nThe young man thanked Buzz profusely. He told Buzz that he would be the best student possible and that Buzz would not
        regret helping him.
        \n\nAs it turns out, Buzz would actually be very, very glad he had helped him.
        \n\nThe young man started his business in a simple way, taking orders and delivering honey. Everyone loved the honey, and
        the news about the honey began to spread.
        \n\nNeither the young man nor Buzz knew that the particular combination of flowers and plants in the town made for some of
        the best honey that could be made.
        \n\nSoon, the young man had his own store and his business was more successful than he had ever thought possible from a
        honey store. People began to come from neighboring towns to buy this unique honey. The fame of the honey grew and so did
        the business. And every time people came to try the honey, you know where they got bread to try the honey on? Buzz’s Bakery.
    </string>
    <string name="part_10">
        Buzz continued to help others with his knowledge and his bakery. He never forgot the principles he learned nor those
        who taught him the principles. He was grateful that he had taken risks and grateful that he had taken them wisely. He
        was happy that he had chosen to help others. Those choices had made Buzz’s life a very, very happy one.
        \n\nThat is the end of this story, but there is a much more exciting story waiting for you: real life. What
        will you choose to do next?
    </string>
    <string name="goBack">Start Over</string>
    <string name="theEndText">
        The End
    </string>

</resources>
